[{"answer": "You know, it actually started by a late night conversation over twitter with a woman who was pooh-poohing government's role in provision nutrition for kids.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Why did do you this?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "You know, it's a little more difficult than I imagined and I thought I would be good on eating on a tight budget.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "How are you finding it?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "First of all, I hope people are sniping.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Your reaction?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "There is a real venomous (ph) disconnect here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I'm trying to decide whether having worked through days of headaches, whether I should go intravenous caffeine right away or stay away from this succulently seductive, addictive thing that --", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Where do I send the Starbucks on Monday morning when it's all over for you?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Maybe until -- maybe until he was presented with a stark opportunity to lead.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "So he wasn't a leader until you needed leadership?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think that's the way government should work and that's what we should expect from people.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "I'm sure Mayor Cory Booker has a lot to say about this, because he may be your rival, of course, should you -- you can confirm this now -- but should you come up against Chris Christie politically, what do you make of what's going on with him and the president?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I'm not even going to give you the denial.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Booker v. Christie 2013?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Look, I think he's vulnerable.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Could you beat him?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think if there was a cause, a need for that, I applaud my president.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "How would you feel if the president comes down and puts his arm around him again at the height of the battle?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Again, my focus right now is trying to figure out what that next step will be that is in accordance with my values.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Booker for Senate, 2013?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Of the United States of America.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "President of the New Jersey \"Star Trek\" association?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I can sure you, Piers, no one is snickering or laughing tonight.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What do we actually know about this?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "No, because we don't know the background, we don't know -- there might have been a series of events that culminated in her suicide but were not solely linked to this.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "We don't actually know for sure, I guess at this stage, whether her death is 100 percent linked to what happened, do we?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, suicides are very complicated.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "That's such a difficult question.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "What should be done about this?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "So I would disagree with the premise a little bit.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Quickly, Kristen -- I'll come to you in a moment, Joe -- but do you feel comfortable that the Republicans are prepared to slash investment in something like food stamps in an effort to try and protect -- as it seems to many people -- the wealthiest 2 percent from paying more tax?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Public opinion on this issue has changed very rapidly in sort of just the last 20 years.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Where does that leave the party in four years time, if they try and fight on another platform that doesn't fully support and embrace gay rights in America?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I've been great.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "How have you been?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "It's pretty unbelievable.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "But do you ever stop and think wow, I'm still only 33 and yet I've had this 18-year career?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Oh my God.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What's being a mother like?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "One of the things that I can't -- I can't put my mind around is where she really was because, you know, at the end of her life, I wasn't there.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Or had she just got lost in the maelstrom of fame and abuse and all the rest of it?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I understand what that feels like.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "As somebody who still can, do you understand what that feeling must be like?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I was actually in the same hotel that she passed in.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How did you hear it?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "At the Beverly Hilton?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "It just hit me in ways I can't even explain.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "It hit you that bad?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Ray has been going through it.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "How is Ray doing, because he was very close to her?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Are you excited about having a new album out now, with everything that you've been through in the last 10 years?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I feel everything.", "docId": "121207pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "When you sing, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 559}]